本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
丧尸进攻
"Zombie attack"?
得了吧  他们无组织无纪律
Never works. They don't take orders.
“血雨” 哼  搞不好把我的衣服都搞脏了
"Blood rain"? Ew. Mess up my suit.
哈  得了
Ha. No, thank you.
“恶魔毛虫” 这也太便宜他们了
"Demon caterpillars"? Snap!
一定能想出个天衣无缝的方法
There must be a perfect way to
对派恩斯家族实施一次复仇
exact vengeance on the Pines family.
仅仅伤害他们是不够的
It's not enough to harm 'em.
我还得从他们那儿拿一些东西
I need to take somethin' from 'em,
一种能带给我最强大力量的东西
Somethin' that will give me ultimate power.
等等  我想到了
Wait, of course!
神秘小屋
太完美了
It's perfect.
这次你也太过分了  鸭侦探
You've gone too far this time, Ducktective.
欢迎来到神秘世界
Welcome to a world of mystery--
斯坦・派恩斯
Stan Pines?
收税的  你竟然找到我了
The tax collector! You found me!
这些个门里边儿哪个是活动门
Which one of these is the trap door?
派恩斯先生
Mr. Pines...
我是优惠券储蓄大赛颁奖处的
I'm from the winninghouse coupon savers contest,
你就是我们的大赢家
And you are our big winner!
啊
Heh?
我的唯一的梦想
My one and only dream,
就是能够拥有大把的钞票  现在终于实现了
Which was to possess money, has come true!
我们有钱了  我想要雇个男管家
We're rich! I'm gonna get a butler!
我打算买一个会说话的马
I'm gonna buy a talking horse!
只要在这儿签字就行了
Just sign here for the money.
没问题
You bet!
啊  哈
Uhh! Ha!
斯坦福  你个傻帽
Stanford, you fool!
你刚刚把神秘小屋签约转让给我了
You just signed over the mystery shack to widdle ol' me!
恰恰  恰  恰
Achacha cha cha
啊  我想你还是再仔细看看吧
Ah, might wanna take another look there.
“小屋特此转让给
"The shack is hereby signed over to...
见鬼去吧  小矮人”
Suck a lemon, little man."
呃  你有种
Uhh! How dare you!
你们绝对不能低估我的能耐
I am not a threat to be taken lightly!
过来  亲爱的  借用下你的手臂
Come here, hon, I need your arms.
我会报复你的  斯坦福・派恩斯
I'll get you, Stanford Pines.
报复死你们
I'll get you all!
想看看电视上还有什么吗
Want to see what else is on tv?
嗯  行  那好吧
Yeah, okay. Yeah, all right.
一定很有趣  主题歌可是我最喜欢的部分
Should be fun. My favorite part's the theme song.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： Dai  Sigrid
校订： line  WaitinZ
■
后期： line  chocolate  liloelva
怪诞小镇  第一季第十一集
Gravity Falls  S01E11  Little Dipper
小兵走到第九暗格
Little guy to black space nine.
这是个“兵” 那不是你该走的颜色
It's a "Pawn," That's not your color,
而且别再偷我的马了
And stop stealing the tiny horses.
他们更喜欢呆在这儿
They like it better in here.
是不是啊  小宝贝们
Don't you, babies?
那  将军
And... Checkmate!
什么  逊毙了
What? Boo!
噢  迪普又赢了
Ohh! Dipper wins again!
哟  梅宝  能把那罐子里的脑子递给我吗
Yo, Mabel, can you pass me that brain in the jar?
- 女士的那个  - 我拿吧
- The lady one.  - I got it.
谢了  但是梅宝更高点儿
Thanks, but Mabel's taller.
什么  不  她没我高
What? No, she's not.
我俩一样高  一直都是这样儿
We're the same height. We've always been.
最好是再量一量  兄弟
Better check again, dude.
是的  她恰好比你高一毫米
Yup. She's got exactly one millimeter on you.
什么  喔...
What?! Whoa...
难道你没觉察到正在发生什么吗  迪普
Don't you see what's happening, Dipper?
这一毫米只是个开始
This millimeter is just the beginning.
我正进化成更优秀的姐姐
I'm evolving into the superior sibling.
更大个儿
Bigger...
更强壮
Stronger...
好比更强力的双胞胎
Like some kind of alpha twin.
同胞中的老大  老大
Alpha twin! Alpha twin!
得了吧  两位  实际上没人使用毫米
C'mon, guys, nobody even uses millimeters.
（注：美国一般使用英制单位，加拿大使用公制单位）
你只是在加拿大比我高而已
It only makes you taller than me in Canada.
你知道吗  迪普  我一直想要个小弟弟
You know, Dipper, I've always wanted a little brother.
谁知道我已经有啦
Who knew I already had one!
哈哈哈  耶
Hahaha! Yeah!
我被谁的嘲笑声吵醒了
I was awoken by the sound of mockery.
那人在哪儿
Where is it?
让我看看被嘲弄的对象
Show me the object of ridicule!
我比迪普要高  高了一毫米
I'm taller than Dipper. By one millimeter!
（注：get short with愿意为“对……无礼”）
嘿  嘿  别  比你妹妹矮
Hey, hey. Don't get... Short with your sister.
现在  斯坦叔公
Now, Grunkle Stan...
我希望你不要轻视他
I hope you don't think...Little of him!
哈哈  是  还有  那个  呃
Haha! Yeah! And, and, uh...
他很矮
He's short!
哥们儿  可以别那么咄咄逼人了吧
Dudes, maybe you should lay off a tiny bit.
哈  小不点儿  现在连苏斯也加入我们了
Hah! "Tiny!" Soos is in on it now!
不  我不是那样的意思
No, I didn't mean that.
迪普会忘记的
Dipper will forget.
他有  三  二  一
He's got a--3-2-1...
健忘症
Short-term memory!
啪  我们太牛逼了
Pow! We are on fire!
噢  喔  那太  啊
Ow...Ooh... That's...Aww...
我击掌太猛了
I high-five hard.
呃  梅宝个蠢蛋
Ugh... Stupid Mabel.
我才不矮呢
I'm not short!
呃  呃  噢  拜托
Unh. Unh. Oh, come on!
这上面必定会有变高的办法
There's gotta be some way to get taller.
看看
Let's see...
微小水牛和硕大松鼠的传奇
"Legends of miniature buffalo and giant squirrels
已经使我相信
"Have led me to believe
在森林的深处
"There are height-altering properties
藏着能改变高度的神秘物品
hidden deep within the forest."
那只美洲狮是真小  还是离我太远了所以看着小
Is that mountain lion tiny or just far away in perspective?
距离问题  距离问题  啊
Perspective! Perspective! Aah!
还是疼  但是轻多了
It still hurts, but less!
真见鬼
What the heck.
小小小
Smaller.
大大大
Bigger.
太大了
Too big!
我最近都在买大尺寸的衣服
I've been buying big clothes.
我马上就会长大穿进去了
I'll grow into them.
嘿  伙计们  发现我身上有什么变化没
Hey, guys. Notice anything different about me?
我的天神啊
Holy hot sauce!
你长高了一毫米
You've grown an extra millimeter!
什  什  什么
Wha-wha-whhaaat?
还有什么好说的呢  妹妹  生长突增没办法
What can I say, sis? Growth spurt.
呃  我的突增期先到的
Eh, mine happened first.
我最后肯定会比你高的
I'm gonna be taller in the end.
科学注定如此  迪普
It's science, Dipper.
什么  但我们现在一样高了
What? But we're the same height now.
双胞胎老大  老大
Alpha twin! Alpha twin!
噢  耶
Oh, yeah?
我有预感
Something tells me I've
我的另一个生长期马上又要来了
got another growth spurt coming on right now.
放弃吧  迪普
Give it up, Dipper.
发生了什么
What happened!?
你知道的  青春期什么的
You know... Puberty and stuff.
这根本讲不通啊
It doesn't make any sense!
一秒钟前你还  等等
Just a second ago you were-- wait a minute.
肯定是魔力作祟  对不对
This is some kind of magicky thing, isn't it?
是个魔法师还是什么
Was it a wizard or something?
衣柜里面肯定有魔法师
There's a wizard in this closet,
- 有没有  有没有  - 什么  没有
- Isn't there? Isn't there?  - What? No!
你说柜子里面没有巫师
You're telling me there is not a wizard in this closet?
你说如果我现在打开这扇门
You're telling me that if I open this door right now--
好  打开吧
Fine! Open it!
一个隐身的魔法师  是不是啊  迪普
An invisible wizard! Really, Dipper?
哦  是你
Oy. You.
您好  斯坦福  听好了
Howdy, Stanford! Listen closely.
在这个罐子里面
Inside this jar,
我放了一千只被诅咒过的埃及超级白蚁
I have 1,000 cursed Egyptian super termites.
交出你的房产证
Hand over the deed to your property
要不然我就一棒子打烂这个罐子
Or I'll smash this jar with a bat
它们会把你和这间小屋一齐吞噬掉
And they'll devour the shack with you inside.
嘿  那是什么  呃
Hey, what's that? Huh?
噢  不
oh, no!
啊哈  快走开
Aaahh! Get it off!
哈哈哈  嘿  苏斯  快过来
Ha ha ha! Hey, soos, get in here!
我想给这哥们儿拍张照片
I wanna take pictures of this!
这次也许你赢了
You may have won the battle,
但是记住我的话  斯坦福
But mark my words, Stanford,
你的家族肯定有弱点  我一定会找出来的
Your family has a weak spot, and I'm gonna to find it.
啊啊  我的头发
Aaughh! My hair!
难道他只对咒语有反应吗
Does he only respond to incantations?
呼唤巫师
Expecto wizarium!
魔法  魔法
Wizzle... Wizar...
和魔法师无关
It's not a wizard!
我是用魔法手电筒帮我长高的
I grew myself using this magic flashlight!
让我瞧瞧那东西
Let me see that thing!
迟早我会回来找你算账的
I'll be back for you later!
没事儿  它也能让东西变小
It's okay. It can shrink things, too.
看我空手道
Normal-hand-karate-chop
嘿  把它还给我
Hey, give it back!
喔啊  决不
Whoa! Never!
派恩斯家族去死
Curse the Pines family!
斯坦去死  迪普去死
Curse Stan! Curse Dipper!
诅咒
Curse....
天哪  天哪
My, my,
这是个什么讨人欢喜的小玩意儿啊
What delightful manner of doohickery is this?
也许他没见到我们怎么用这东西的
Maybe he didn't see us use it
而且不知道这是个可以
And doesn't know it's a magic flashlight
使东西变大变小的魔力手电筒
That can grow and shrink things.
真的吗
Really?
点击  嘣  吼  吼
Click. Boop. Hoo hoo.
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no!!!
朋友们  我希望我是一条高速公路
Friends, I wish I was a highway
那样我就有幸能被
so I could have the honor of being rode upon
像这般出众的汽车疾驰奔腾在我身上
by automobiles as fine as these ones right ch'er.
引擎老鼠不额外收费哦亲
Engine possum at no extra charge.
我想要那车
I want that thar car!
是  我也要
Yeah, me, too!
别动  儿子  罐子里面是什么
Say there, son, what's in the jar?
这是我的小秘密
That's my widdle secret!
一群低能儿
Mouth-breathing fools.
妈妈
Mother.
你们两个
You two.
你  你要对我俩做什么
What-- what are you going to do with us?
干嘛呢  梅宝  我不会动你一根头发
Why, Mabel, I wouldn't hurt a hair on your itty bitty head.
如果你同意做我的皇后
If you agree to be my queen!
我们现在生活在民主社会中
We live in a democracy.
我决不同意
And never!
试过这个之后也许你就会同意了
Maybe you'll change your mind after this.
不  我将和你抗争到我
No! I will fight you until the day I...
考拉QQ糖
gummy koalas!
至于你吗  小子
As for you, boy...
告诉我
Tell me,
你究竟是怎么得到这个魔力手电筒的  嗯
How exactly did you come upon this magic item, hmm?
有人告诉过你关于这玩意儿的事儿吗
Did somebody tell you about it?
还是你在哪儿读过关于它的事情
Did you read about it somewhere?
靠近点我就告诉你
Lean closer and I'll tell you.
好吧  不要介意我
well, don't mind if I--
我现在就可以拍扁你
I could squash you right now!!
冷静点儿  吉迪恩
Steel yourself, Gideon.
你可以利用他们
You can use them.
你能利用他们
苏斯  这个镜子迷宫是迄今为止
Soos, this maze of mirrors is your best idea
我最为你感到骄傲的点子
that I'm taking credit for yet!
我们就要发财了
We're gonna make a fortune!
我的耳朵一直这么大么
My ears always been this big?
来了
I'm comin'!
总有一天
One day...
斯坦福・派恩斯
Stanford Pines.
你最好给我仔细听好咯  你的侄孙子侄孙女现在在我手里
Listen to me very closely, I have your niece and nephew.
马上交出神秘小屋的房契
Hand over the deed to the mystery shack right now
否则将有大难降临于他们
Or great harm will befall them.
顺便说一句  我是吉迪恩
This is Gideon, by the way.
哦  是吗  这是你最失策的诡计了
Oh, yeah. This has gotta be your worst plot yet.
他们很好啊
They're fine.
几分钟之前我还看到他们在院子里玩
I saw them playing in the yard minutes ago.
他们在我手里
I have them in my possession.
你不相信我
You don't believe me?!
我短信一张照片给你
I will text you a photo.
“短信”我一张“照片”
"Text" me a "photo"?
你现在连英语都不会说了啊
Now you're not even speaking English.
但是
But--
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?!
我在做什么啊
What am I doing?
我有这个  还需要什么赎金
I don't need ransom. I have this!
我要把斯坦变小  这样就可以独享神秘小屋啦
I'll shrink Stan and take the shack for myself!
你们都没法阻止我
You'll all be helpless to stop me.
如果你们敢越界行事  小心被我捏碎
And if any of you step out of line... Smash!
吉迪恩
Gideon!
冰淇淋车来了
The ice cream truck is here!
噢  来啦  嘻嘻嘻
Oh! Coming! Hehehe!
仓鼠  给我看好他们
Guard them, cheekums.
我来啦
I'm coming!
我们得赶快离开这里  好救救斯坦叔公
We got to get out of here and save Stan.
这我也知道啊
I know!
一会儿跟你碰面
I will see you later.
好  我们要怎么办
Ok, how are we going to do this?
吉迪恩现在手上有魔法手电筒  把我们缩小了那么多
Gideon's got magic and like a zillion inches on us.
往好的一面想呢  至少我们终于又一样高了
On the bright side, at least we're finally the same height again.
其实
Actually...
怎么还是你更高
You're still taller?!
啊  这怎么可能
Argh! How did this happen?
我想这是另外一个迷吧
I guess it's another mystery.
也是我们要赶快夺回那个手电筒的原因
Just another reason we gotta get that flashlight back.
小仓鼠  我们走
Cheekums, to freedom!
奔向自由
To freedom!
你实在笨死了啊
You're just a big ol' dummy-dum!
我有个计划
I have a plan.
帮我擦嘴
Clean me!
爸爸  你能送我一程
Father, could you give widdle ol' me
去神秘小屋么
a "wide" to the mystery shack?
喔  我很乐意啊宝贝
Ohhh, I'd love to, sugar pie,
但我有好多车要卖啊  不骗你
But I have a heck of a lot of cars to sell, I do.
不  不要  别挠我痒
No, no! Don't tickle me!
不要啊
No!
千万千万别再挠我痒了
Never! Never tickle me!
我跟你怎么说的
What have I told you?
我说过的  你看我
What have I-- look at me.
我没警告过你吗
What have I told you?
挠痒痒可不是闹着玩的
Tickling is no laughing matter.
这就对了
There we go.
还需要载你一程么
Do you still need a ride?
我坐公交好了
I'll just take the bus!
多珍贵的回忆啊
Precious memories.
继续吸尘  继续吸尘
Just keep vacuuming... Just keep vacuuming.
快  啊
C'mon! Uhh.
我们得站高一点儿
We need to get higher.
是  尤其是你  因为你很矮
Yeah, especially you 'cause you're short.
梅宝  去那上面
Mabel! Up there.
你这小可爱要去哪里啊
What cute little thing are you off to,
你这个可爱的小可爱
You cute little cutey-face?
我要去歼灭我大敌的全家
I'm going to annihilate my archenemy's entire family!
哦  好吧
Ohh! Okay!
耶
Yaayyy.
他要去缩小斯坦了
He's heading to shrink Stan!
噢  折扣美金气球
Oh, flying discount dollar,
如果你能带我们飞回到神秘小屋就好了
If only you could fly us back to the mystery shack.
说不定可以
Maybe it can.
我的天价气球
My sky-high prices!
到底下去
Down there!
向神秘小屋前进
To the mystery shack!
我们来的正好
We're just in time.
不过我们要怎么才能阻止他
But how are we going to stop him?
交给梅宝了
Leave that to Mabel!
我找你报仇来了  斯坦福  噢
I'm comin' for ya, Stanford-- ohh!
不好意思哦  QQ糖
I'm sorry, gummy friend!
为了大义只能牺牲掉了
It's for the greater good.
噢  有颗该死的考拉QQ糖
Ow! One of those infernal gummy koalas
掉到我帅气无边的头发里了
Has gotten into my perfect hair!
我不能这个鬼样子去收拾斯坦
I can't defeat Stan looking like this!
赶紧的  站到前面  我把你重新变大
Quick. Get in front and I'll re-grow you.
好  等下
Okay-- wait.
你应该是把我们变回一样高吧
You're gonna grow us back to the equal height, right?
迪普  这个现在不重要
Dipper, that doesn't matter right now!
好  如果这不重要
Well, if it doesn't matter,
那你就把我们变回一样高吧
then why don't you just do it?
啊  你现在真是奇怪
Aah! Why are you acting so weird?
你为什么就不能承认我比你高一点点呢
Why can't you just accept that I'm a little bit taller than you?
噢  我很奇怪吗
Oh, I'm acting weird?!
是你总出口伤人给我起外号
You're the one who keeps calling me names and stuff!
噢  什么  你是说像小
Oh, what? You mean like little--
不要说出来
Don't say it!
小迪普
Little Dipper.
我敢说要不是你们兄妹争吵
I dare say you would have defeated me,
我肯定败在你们手里了
If it wasn't for your sibling bickering!
啊  小屋是我的  斯坦福・派恩斯
Aah! The shack is mine, Stanford Pines!
不要啊
No!
好了  好了  斯坦福
Well, well, Stanford,
好似我终于打败
It appears I've finally gotten the best of--
-啊  -什么
- Huh? - What?
好吧  肯定哪里不对劲了
All right, something's definitely different here.
快说斯坦在哪
Tell me where Stan is!
妄想  你永远也找不到
Never! You'll never find Stan
在门廊左边第二个门里的斯坦的
On the second door to the left down the hall.
呃  完了  我干嘛说出来啊
Uh, wait, why did I say that?
斯坦福  我来找你咯
Stanford, I'm coming for ya!
我想我又犯老毛病了  不是么
I guess I kinda Soosed that one up, didn't I?
不是你的错  苏斯
It's not your fault, soos.
是我组装了那个手电筒
I'm the guy who put together that shrinking device.
我想只是
I guess it's just...
你老开我玩笑  梅宝  几乎从早到晚
You kept teasing me, Mabel. Like, all day.
这都是为什么啊
What was that all about?
我想是
I guess it's that...
你好像什么事情都比我做得好
You're better than me at like everything.
并且你还总当着我的面重复个不停
And you always rub it in my face.
象棋  跳棋  乒乓
Chess, checkers, ping pong.
我觉得终于有一次我有比你强的地方了
I guess I finally felt like I was winning at something for once.
哦  天呐  我觉得自己很混蛋啊
Aw, man, now I feel like a big jerk.
你说的是  小混蛋吗
Don't you mean... A little jerk?
好吧  我自己跳进陷阱了
All right, I walked into that one.
那我们和好了
Are we cool?
和好如初
We're cool.
我酷吗
Am I cool?
你很酷  苏斯
You're cool, Soos.
太好了
Yes!
斯坦福
Stanford!
哦  嗨  吉迪恩
Oh, hi, Gideon!
我一直在找人帮忙试验我新开发的镜子迷宫
I've been looking for someone to try out my new mirror maze.
然后强调一下  你真是个白痴
Then again, you're an idiot.
我说完了
That's the end of the sentence.
你给我出来
You come back here!
试试来找我啊  蠢货  哈哈哈
Try and find me, twerp. Ha ha ha!
我们得在吉迪恩抓到斯坦之前把手电筒拿到手
Let's get that flashlight before Gideon gets Stan.
在那儿呢
There it is!
喔  他的头发好闪亮好有光泽
Whoa, his hair's so shiny.
别  别直视它
No! Don't look directly at it!
他的脖子好粘糊啊
This neck is really squishy.
嗨  看呐  我成天使了
Hey, look! I'm making fat angels!
唉呀  白蚁
Ew! Termites!
记得提起我
Tell my story!
噢
Ohh.
嗨  你在这呢
Hey, there you are!
以为你会离开我呢  呵  玉米片
Thought you could get away from me, eh, corn chip?
不
No!
嗨  别乱砸啊
Hey, watch the merchandise!
你个小侏儒
You little troll!
这些镜子花了我十
These mirrors cost me ten--
我想想  呃  二十  五  五百
I mean, uh, twenty-- five-- five hundred--
每个五百美金
Five hundred dollars each.
现在你全都要赔
And you're paying for all of 'em!
正好相反
Au contraire,
付出代价的应该是你
It'll be you who pays.
斯坦叔公要完蛋了
Grunkle Stan is doomed!
不完全是  去他的胳肢窝
Not completely doomed! To his armpit!
你就  呃  走
Just...Unh, c'mon!
喔  这是个什么玩意儿
Whoa, what is that thing?
终于啊  这么些年了  受尽了你的羞辱
Finally, after all these years, after every humiliation!
你的生意  你的家庭  所有的一切都终将归我所有
Your business, your family, everything will finally be mine!
没有人可以保护你了
You have no one to protect you now!
准备被吉迪恩的愤怒给
Prepare for the wrath of Gideon glee...
吉迪恩
Gideon glee..
呃  我甚至接不上你的话
Uh, I don't even know how to respond to this.
咿  咿  不要啊
Hee hee, no!
住手
stop it!
孩子啊
Look, uh, kid.
我了解这个竞争的事情很影响你
I think this rivalry thing is getting to you.
哈  我很能理解
Ha. I understand.
我是说  我确实是个强大的劲敌  要怎么说呢
I mean, I'm a formidable foe, what can I say.
别啊  哈哈哈哈哈
No--ah hahahahah!
嘿  快别闹了
Hey, now. Come on.
也许以后你能整到我
You'll get me one of these days.
也许  让你的朋友
Maybe, you know, run your evil plan
来施行你的恶魔计划  怎么样
by some friends next time, huh?
研讨一下
Workshop it.
但首先要罗列一下你们的问题
But first get your issues in order there.
起  起来
Get...Up, up.
到地毯那边去  那边那边
Over the carpet, there we go.
啊  然后再在边边打个滚
Uhh. Around the end table,
然后  嗯  滚出去吧
And, uh, out the door.
我的手电筒
My light...
你也是我的生命之光啊  朋友
You're the light of my life, too, pal.
喔  怪胎秀
Whoo! Freak show.
你先
After you.
没事  你想变就你先  哇
It's okay. You can go first if you want-- whoa!
嘿  你还把我变得比你高那么一毫米啊
Hey! You let me keep my extra millimeter.
是你的努力换来的
You earned it.
嗯  谢啦  小哥哥
Ah, thanks, "Little brother"--
求你别叫
Stop it.
我想我们应该毁了这个东西
I guess we should destroy this thing.
这样就不会落入坏人的手中了
You know, so it doesn't fall into the wrong hands and junk.
看起来这样做是明智的
Seems like the smart thing to do.
毁掉  毁掉
Die, die!
伙计们  你们在这儿啊
There you dudes are!
我一直想引起你们的注意啊
I been tryin' to get your attention!
-胶水  -好多的胶水
- Glue. - Lots of glue.
孩子  你别把斯坦福・派恩斯那事太放在心上
Oh, son, don't you mind that Stanford Pines.
你定有一天能报仇的
You'll get your revenge one of these days.
不是  这不仅仅是报仇的问题
No! It's not just about revenge!
我要小屋  是小屋
I want that shack. The physical building.
为什么呢
But why?
因为它藏有你无法想象的秘密
Because it holds a secret you couldn't possibly imagine.
噢  宝贝儿  你要来点冰淇淋吗
Uh, sweetie, you want some ice cream?
你把坚果都挑出来了吗
Did you pick out all the nuts?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
再来一勺
Lil' more?
挺好
That's good.
派恩斯先生
Mr. Pines,
我们是优惠券储蓄大奖颁奖处的
I'm from the winninghouse coupon savers contest
您是我们的大奖得主
And you are our big winner!
我想我们得把奖转送到亚军得主
I guess we'll have to give the prize to our runner-up winner...
菲德福特・麦戈科特
Fiddleford H. McGucket?
你想要一千万美元吗
How would you like ten million dollars?
我的美梦成真了啊
It's my dream come true!
把这个镇子的人从名单上都排除吧
Cross this town off our list.